const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'Beta testing is:',
    answer: [ 'Performed by customers at their own site',
              'Performed by customers at their software developer’s site',
              'Performed by an independent test team',
              'Useful to test bespoke software',
              'Performed as early as possible in the lifecycle'
            ],
    correctAnswer: 'Performed by customers at their own site',
  },
  {
    question: 'The main focus of acceptance testing is:',
    answer: [ 'finding faults in the system',
              'ensuring that the system is acceptable to all users',
            	'testing the system with other systems',
	            'testing for a business perspective',
	            'testing by an independent test team'
            ],
    correctAnswer: 'testing for a business perspective'
  },
  {
    question: 'Equivalence partitioning is:',
    answer: [ 'A black box testing technique used only by developers',
	            'A black box testing technique than can only be used during system testing',
              'A black box testing technique appropriate to all levels of testing',
	            'A white box testing technique appropriate for component testing'
            ],
    correctAnswer: 'A black box testing technique than can only be used during system testing'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a static testing technique?',
    answer: [ 'A	Error guessing',
            	'Walkthrough',
              'Data flow analysis',
	            'Inspections'
            ],
    correctAnswer: 'A	Error guessing'
  },
  {
    question: 'Statement Coverage will not check for the following:',
    answer: [ 'Missing Statements',
	            'Unused Branches',
              'Dead Code',
        	    'Unused Statement'
        	  ],
    correctAnswer: 'Missing Statements'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which is NOT true -  The black box tester:',
    answer: [ 'should be able to understand a functional specification or requirements document',
	            'should be able to understand the source code',
              'is highly motivated to find faults',
	            'is creative to find the system’s weaknesses',
	           ],
	 correctAnswer: 'should be able to understand the source code'
  },
  {
    question: 'Determine the statement which holds true in case of Exploratory Testing:',
    answer: [ 'It starts the execution only when the design gets finalized',
	            'It involves simultaneous design of the test and execution',
	            'It starts the execution only when the design gets renewed',
	            'It starts the execution only when the design gets amended'
	          ],
	 correctAnswer: 'It involves simultaneous design of the test and execution'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which testing phase tests individual software modules combined together as a group?',
    answer: [ 'Module testing',
	            'Integration testing',
	            'White Box testing',
	            'Software testing'
	           ],
	 correctAnswer: 'Integration testing'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is not part of performance testing?',
    answer: [ 'Measuring response time',
              'Measuring transaction rates',
              'Recovery testing',
	            'Simulating many users',
	            'Generating many transactions'
	           ],
	 correctAnswer: 'Recovery testing'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a black box technique?',
    answer: [ 'Equivalence partitioning',
	            'State transition testing',
	            'Linear code sequence and jump',
	            'Syntax testing',
              'Boundary value analysis'
            ],
    correctAnswer: 'Linear code sequence and jump'
  }
  
  ];